var title = 'Traduza para grego.<br>Para substantivos, inclua o artigo definido (ο, η, το...).';

var questions = [

 {
   prompt: "a saúde",
   answer: ["η υγεία", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "inglês (a língua)",
   answer: ["τα αγγλικά", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o basquete",
   answer: ["το μπάσκετ-μπωλ", "το μπάσκετμπολ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o amanhã",
   answer: ["το αύριο", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o milagre",
   answer: ["το θαύμα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "(eu) trabalho",
   answer: ["δουλέυω", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "o Euro (moeda)",
   answer: ["το Ευρώ", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a palavra",
   answer: ["η λέξη", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a terra",
   answer: ["η γη", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a hora",
   answer: ["η ώρα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

 {
   prompt: "a imagem",
   answer: ["η εικόνα", ],
   partial: [], 
 },

];